Is anyone going to riot? Is anyone going to try to shoot them in the face?
If someone goes into a building full of people in the middle of the night covering their faces without identification, without identifying themselves,
there might be concern among the community, especially if American citizens are being, especially if American citizens are caught up in that, which some importantly were.
We netted over 30 foreign terrorists who are members of Trained Uruguay.
And American citizens also wound up apprehended in that.
They torture women and children. Those American citizens are now safe from Trained Uruguay.
You know, there was a case recently in Washington state.
But isn't that enough reason for some people to demonstrate and say that they disagree with that policy?
They took a power drill.
Isn't it enough for some people?